shopdaily.pk 2017-12-07

# Tohfay.com-Privacy Policy

| 

|  SHOPDAILY.pk Privacy Policy  
---  
  
At SHOPDAILY.pk we take extreme care in preserving the important personal information coming to us from our customers. The information submitted to SHOPDAILY.pk will not be revealed to any third party except where it is required for transactions.

Information collected during Registration process such as, e-mail address, telephone number, address and a valid credit card number is used only to verify customer's account and to process the orders. The information collected is not sold or rented to any third parties except for transactions involving third parties. The third parties are not permitted to sell, rent or share this information.  
  
**Use of Your Email Address**  
  
We only use our customer's e-mails to communicate with them regarding the details of their order, their shipping information and or any other customer service related issues. We will occasionally send our customers e-mail with recommendations or notices of new products and prices. 

SHOPDAILY.pk does not trade, rent or sell your personal information to others. We share customer information only with members of SHOPDAILY.pk family of businesses to provide you with products or services that you have requested or to provide you with promotional offers that we believe will be of interest to you. The SHOPDAILY.pk family of businesses includes all SHOPDAILY.pk affiliates as well as other selected businesses with which SHOPDAILY.pk has a relationship and which perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, sending postal mail and e-mail, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to this data only to perform their operational or other support functions, but may not use it for other purposes. We also may provide information to regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials in accordance with applicable law or when we otherwise believe in good faith that the law requires it. In the event of a sale of all or part of our businesses, we may share customer information related to that business as part of the transaction.  
  
**Does SHOPDAILY.pk use cookies?**  
  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored either in your browser or on your hard drive. SHOPDAILY.pk uses only "session" cookies. This means that we never store information on your computer and the information we do send to your browser is gone when you close the browser. These cookies allow us to make sure that only you can see your data and to provide you with a customized experience on our web sites that we feel will be of value to you. Most web browsers allow you to control this use of cookies. Please take a look at your particular browser for instructions on this function. If you elect to disable cookies please keep in mind that you will not be able to order product from our site or take full advantage of a personalized experience at our web sites.  
  
**How can I access my personal information?**  
  
You can access your personal information at anytime to update, correct, add or delete any of the data you have shared with us. If you are a registered user, you can access your personal information by clicking on the "My Account" link at the top of any web page. Your account information is secure and is accessible by only using a password that you select.   
  
**Can I "opt out" of receiving e-mails from SHOPDAILY.pk?**  
  
SHOPDAILY.pk may send you e-mails only if you opt-in to receive such e-mails. If you select to receive email notifications and later chose not you can simply opt-out. You will be given the opportunity to opt-out in every email notification.  
  
**TERMS OF USE**  
  
This Web site may contain links to web sites controlled by parties other than SHOPDAILY.pk. SHOPDAILY.pk is not responsible for and does not endorse or accept any responsibility for the contents or use of these third party web sites. SHOPDAILY.pk is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by SHOPDAILY.pk of the linked web site. It is your responsibility to take precautions to ensure that whatever you select for your use is free of viruses or other items of a destructive nature.

You understand that all information, data, text, software, music, sound, photographs, graphics, video, messages or other materials ("Content"), whether publicly posted or privately transmitted, are the sole responsibility of the person from which such Content originated. This means that you, and not SHOPDAILY.pk, are entirely responsible for all Content that you upload, post, email, transmit or otherwise make available via the Service. SHOPDAILY.pk does not control the Content posted via the Service and, as such, does not guarantee the accuracy, integrity or quality of such Content. You understand that by using the Service, you may be exposed to Content that is offensive, indecent or objectionable. Under no circumstances will SHOPDAILY.pk be liable in any way for any Content, including, but not limited to, for any errors or omissions in any Content, or for any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of the use of any Content posted, emailed, transmitted or otherwise made available via the Service.   
  
**You agree to not use the Service to:**  
  
Make available any Content that is unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, tortuous, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, libelous, invasive of another's privacy, hateful, or racially, ethnically or otherwise objectionable;

Harm minors in any way; Impersonate any person or entity, including, but not limited to, a SHOPDaily.pk official, or falsely state or otherwise misrepresent your affiliation with a person or entity;

Forge headers or otherwise manipulate identifiers in order to disguise the origin of any Content transmitted through the Service;

Make available any Content that you do not have a right to make available under any law or under contractual or fiduciary relationships (such as inside information, proprietary and confidential information learned or disclosed as part of employment relationships or under nondisclosure agreements);

Make available any Content that infringes any patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright or other proprietary rights ("Rights") of any party;

Make available any unsolicited or unauthorized advertising, promotional materials, "junk mail," "spam," â€œMLM,â€ "chain letters," "pyramid schemes," or any other form of solicitation, except in those areas that are designated for such purpose;

Make available any material that contains software viruses, AdWare, SpyWare, or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment;

Interfere with or disrupt the Service or servers or networks connected to the Service, or disobey any requirements, procedures, policies or regulations of networks connected to the Service;

"Stalk" or otherwise harass another individual; or

Collect or store personal data about other users.
